[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Klein"]}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "What exactly came out today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Well, every witness, starting with the opening statements, Piers, but every witness so far that's taken the stand, except for one lawyer, the defense has gotten Klein out there and today they really struck, if you will, from their standpoint.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "But the side effect of Demerol and the reason it's so significant is that it had a big impact on someone's ability to have a good sleep, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "A little intoxicated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Estimate for us how many times a week you would do that, take him to Dr. Klein's office?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "It could fluctuate.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Klein"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jermaine Jackson"]}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "I mean are you still feeling as confident given that evidence today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, yes, because what Jermaine Jackson -- his point was, and it's well taken, that audio recording that we heard in court was so dramatic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Now why would he not do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, this is what the prosecution really hammered on with both of the witnesses that were in the house and out of the house during that time where there was chaos.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "What are your thoughts about it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "ARWICK: I have not taken to even watch this fiasco.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Where were you when you heard that Michael had died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "I was at home.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "How could it be -- is it possible that Michael could have been a drug addict without anyone around him who cared about him really knowing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I don't think so, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "What is your gut feeling, Dionne, tell you has gone down here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dionne"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "He was wonderful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Super confident boy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Very precocious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Did you know from that stage, when you watched him, did you think he was going to turn out to be this extraordinarily gifted performer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Oh, undoubtedly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "He had a unique talent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Unmistakably.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Did any part of Michael, his story and everything, play into your thinking for you with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "You know, not for me it didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "And his growing years as a drummer and how he went on and on to play with some of the greats in our industry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Is that the intention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Exactly the intention.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I love that man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Do you think he's going to win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "You're the most angry man in -- probably in the world, aren't you, Lewis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "I would hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lewis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "You want water?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "No, nothing will help.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Who do you most fear becoming the Republican nominee on the basis they could then become president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Sarah Palin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Because -- I don't think she exists.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What do you mean not exists?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "She doesn't exist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "You couldn't invent someone like Sarah Palin, could you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Well, I mean, that's really what makes her superfiction.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Why is she able to resonate with so many Americans in a positive way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Well, first off I don't know how many Americans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Have you ever gotten a phone call from somebody asking you your opinion of anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "No, but I'm British.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Isn't she a female Lewis Black?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lewis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Why has it become so angry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "I think in part because they have listened to the Tea Party, to the point they've given a disproportion in amount of power much the way in the '60s when I was a kid in college.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Why does that make you a bad president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, because they didn't sit down and talk to the Republicans and do whatever it is that the Republicans think that they wanted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Why has the American business model gone so badly wrong so quickly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Because we -- I think we graduate kids who don't know how to add or subtract.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", ":", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "``", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Do you ever have had moments of calm, quiet happiness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "LACK: When -- there are moments like when they're going to tell me -- I know there are moments that are coming, when they say to me, \"Keeping up With The Kardashians\" is going off the air.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Why did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I thought you were dying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Goldie, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "I'm so well, thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Is it really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "I swear to God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Do gentlemen prefer blondes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Why after 9/11?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Well, 9/11 was sort of the catalyst, I guess you could say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "What are the key things from this book that you think parents need to know about children, that perhaps they haven't thought about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "I think that the one thing is they have to -- it isn't about children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "How much of that creates this kind of anxiety to young people, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Well, the brain actually has a tremendous amount to do with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Do they care?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "No, they said don't get married, it's great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Does it just have a bad effect on people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "I think that getting back to some of the stuff I'm doing -- and I'm not really selling this, but it really all goes into the same theme -- is really emotional intelligence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Or are you now just this bubbly Goldie that we all assume you always are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "I wouldn't call it depression.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Have you enjoyed being out of movies for 10 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Very much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "It's a comedy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VB", "CC", "RB", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 692, "question": "It's an HBO comedy series?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "Here it is: it's a comedy but it actually -- the whole thing will be very deep and really -- but we have a lot of --", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["HBO"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Are you excited to be getting back on the acting saddle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "Yes, I kind of am excited.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "One of them is, how many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "Properly is really kind of the key.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Am I right in thinking husband number two at the moment is being relegated by the hour?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "I do love you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "What a cool thing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "It's just crazy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 753, "question": "But that's sort of an obvious, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "No, I love that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "Can we do it for longer next time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]